A Guide to the James Branch Cabell Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7779-d
James Branch Cabell Collection 1915-1930, n.d.
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7779-d
16 items
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1968 Mar 21
Item Listing
- Letters
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, 1915 Feb 1; TLS, 3 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, 1915 Feb 15; TLS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to [ James Branch Cabell], [1919 Aug] 10; ALS, 2 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, 1919 Aug; ALS, 1 p.
    [Contains poem beginning "Just beneath the misty range..."]
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, [1920] Feb 3; TLS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, [1920]; TLS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, [1920]; TLS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, [1921] May 16; ALS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, [1921] n.m. 19; ALS, 3 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, w/photostat, [1922] Feb 14; TLS, 3 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, 1930 May 4; TLS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, 1930 Aug 13; ALS, 2 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, 1930 Nov 4; TLS, 1 p.
  - "Hal" to James Branch Cabell, n.y. May 4; TLS, 1 p.
  - Sinclair Lewis to James Branch Cabell, n.d.; TLS, 1 p.
- Miscellaneous
  - Description of James Branch Cabell by [ Burton Rascoe], n.d.; Clipping